You can't hide from yourself.
Ghosts of War is a horror, thriller, war film directed by Eric Bress.
A group of World War II American soldiers encounter a supernatural enemy as
they occupy a French castle previously under Nazi control.
Chris, played by Brenton Thwaites.
Kirk, played by Theo Rossi.
Eugene, played by Skylar Astin.
Tappert, played by Kyle Gallner.
Butchie, played by Alan Ritchson.
Dr. Engel, played by Billy Zane.
Ghosts of War is a 2020 British supernatural horror war
film written and directed by Eric Bress.
The film stars Brenton Thwaites, Theo Rossi, Skylar
Astin, Kyle Gallner, and Alan Ritchson.
It was released on DirecTV on 18 June 2020.
The film is about five American soldiers during World War II
who are assigned to guard a French chateau.
They soon realize the house is haunted by the vengeful ghosts
of a family murdered there by German soldiers.
However, the film's plot takes a dramatic twist, revealing that the soldiers are actually modern-day troops in a virtual
reality simulation designed to help them cope with a traumatic event they experienced in Afghanistan.
The ghosts haunting them are not from the past, but the
spirits of the Afghan family they failed to save.
The film explores themes of video game, world war ii,
supernatural, castle, haunted castle.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.